Elcin Quliyev

Python Developer

elcinquliyevm@gmail.com | +994(55)785-62-77 | Azerbaijan, Baku | Github | LinkedIn

Portfolio

Profile

I am a 24 years old software engineer mainly specialized in Python/Django. Being very inspired developer I am looking for new opportunities in my professionalcareer. Currently working in a company as Software Engineer, providing technical support on several projects]simultaneously, mostly based on marketplace-style projects, and guiding students as Web Development Instructor in the evenings.

Professional Experience

Bol-bol.az, Konum-az, Python Developer

08/2023 - present

- In Next.js, routers are automatically set based on the file structure. This makes it easier to organize pages and is convenient to manage large applications.
- React.js offers a component-based approach to UI (user interface). Each component is associated with its own state and behavior. This makes the code easier to manage and reuse.
- Writing a Python script to automate a task (sending email, gathering data)
- Creating a small web app using Django to display products listing or customer informations
- · Assistings in the creation of a Python- based REST APi that interacts with a database

JET Academy - Python Web Development Instructor

05/2023 - present

- Introduction to frameworks like Django for building basic web
- Python fundementals to advanced topics. This may include concepts such as data types, control flow, functions, object-oriented programming (OOP), web development, databases and libraries like NumPy and Pundas.
- · Writing functions, passing parameters and understanding scope and return value
- Encourage teamwork by assingning group projects where students can collaborate and apply Python inn real-world scenarios.

Education

Azerbaijan Cooperative University

09/2017 - 06/2021 | Baku, Azerbaijan

Skills

Back-End — Python, OOP, Django, Django REST Framework, Celery, Redis, RabbitMQ, Flask & FastAPi (experienced), Selenium, PyAutoGUI(Bost Development), Numpy, Pandas, Web Parsing & Scrapping

Front-End — React, JavaScript, Ajax, JQuery, Next.js(experienced), Vue.js(experienced), HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,

Databased - MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Git - GitHub. Bitbucked

Languages

Azerbaijan (native), Turkey (native), English(A2), Rus(A1)